One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The clouds floating in the cobalt blue,
got lost and will soak us all tomorrow.
It'll be fine if you just smile before the sunset.
If it's your wish, you can just
say a spell in your chest.
For your hopes...
Our quick premonition
is showing in the rainbow colored music notes.
Won't you come with me?
We're fallen angels,
we'll fire arrows into your dreams.
What color shall we add
into the cobalt blue?
Destroy the sad reality that reflects in your eyes.
Let's raise our wings, full of warmth.
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts.
Forgive Yourself!
Franky Departs!
You guys, have you made up your minds about Usopp?
This is a matter of pride...
I know that.
How long are you gonna stay depressed?
Shut up!
Why am I the only one with a drawn picture?!
That's an amazing amount for the first time.
Which part of this picture looks like me?!
It looks exactly like you...
Which part of this is me?!
∆ □ x ∑ ≠ € җ Ө ☼
I can't understand your words...
I'll be the laughingstock of the whole world's ladies...
I was tricked...
He said he was the town's magazine reporter.
The picture turned out cute though...
I also got a bounty after all...
I'm also a pirate!
I fought like a true man!
I gotta object to these 50 belly!
Well, try harder next time!
Hurry up!
Don't forget anything!
As soon as we get the ship and Franky, we depart!
Luffy, Sanji isn't moving.
Just forget about that curly guy.
Are you leaving already, pirate guys?
Exceptions among exceptions, aren't they?
For them all to have bounties in such a small crew is...
The total bounty is over 600 million.
By the way...
This man called Black Leg...
Why is there no photo of him?
That...
I certainly took it, but...
When I looked at the developed film, I was surprised...
This is the picture...
It turned out weird...!
Did you take off...
the lens cap?
Brother!
We called them here!
Brother, where are you?!
They came?
Oh! There's something huge over there!
Is that it?!
Hey! We came, Franky!
Please give us the ship!
Oh! Old man Ice!
You came...
Unfortunately, Franky isn't around...
However, the ship is complete.
I'll show it to you in his place.
This ship is amazing.
My eyes were shocked when I saw the amazing blueprints; it's one that can sail over any sea.
With this ship, sailing to the end of the world won't be a dream.
Hurry and show it to us!
Please!
That was a message from Franky, Straw Hat.
If you're going to become the Pirate King someday...
You have to ride this king of beasts!
Amazing!
Is this...?
I see.
Oh! So huge and cool!
It could break out of so many places!
Oh! Are you really gonna give us this?!
It's double the size of Merry!
What a big sail!
Is it a sloop?!
Show me the kitchen! The kitchen!
A splendid ship!
I wonder what kind of big flower is that on the ship's bow.
Well, I was sure it was a lion.
The inside is also awesome!
It's a lawn deck!
Feels so good!
A slide!
You can also do gardening.
Nice for relaxing.
Where's the kitchen?
It must really have mobility with that huge gaff sail!
It's called a brigantine sail.
A sloop is a ship that can sail beyond people's imaginations.
It lives and dies by the order of the navigator.
I'll make my skills roar! I'll do my best!
I also want to take a look.
It has the refrigerator with a lock that I saw in my dreams!
Even a gigantic oven!
Franky, thank you!
This ship is the best!
Hey, old man Ice.
Where's Franky?
I want to thank him.
It seems he doesn't want to see you.
You want to invite him as your shipwright, right?
Yeah.
You got it right.
I've decided he will be my shipwright!
That might be the problem.
He doesn't want to?
The opposite.
If he was invited face to face he wouldn't be able to refuse.
That's why he went to hide.
Well, perhaps his true feelings are to go with you guys out at sea.
You must know pretty well how much he cares for this dream ship he's giving to you.
Oh! There's an aquarium in this place?!
An aquarium? Amazing!
Franky really has a liking for you all from the bottom of his heart.
But he's always thought of it as his duty, staying on this island.
Duty?
Indeed, if you ask me, it's just a stupid obsession.
If you really want him to go with you...
The only method to choose is...
to use force to get him.
That's the only method for his release.
By force?
I want him to go, but...
Is that really okay?!
Brother! Why did you come back?
Do I need a reason?
This is the Franky House!
It's my house!
But...
Are you sure of what you're saying, Brother?!
Doesn't Brother want to go with
Straw Hat-san and the others?!
What a stupid thing to say...
Of course not...!
Hey look!
With skills like yours you can't even build a house.
We just came from asking
Straw Hat-san and the others,
To take Brother out to the sea!
Idiot!
Mind your own business!
But that guy has already decided to take you as his shipwright!
Why do I have to become a pirate?!
You'd know if you could see it!
This is the first time we've seen Brother build a ship, but...
We were amazed you could make such a happy face.
I've never seen Brother have so much fun.
Brother.
You knew the Straw Hats were looking for a shipwright, right?
That's why you ran away, right?!
Look at this, Brother!
A wanted poster!
As I thought, it came out.
It's no use staying with us anymore!
We don't want to be a burden to you!
Stop being so cocky!
What about the marines?!
I'm the one who picked you up from these backstreets when you were dying!
If I'm not here you probably can't probably survive by yourselves...
I got his pants!
Pants?
Why the pants...?
I see!
Don't give them back!
Keep passing the pants!
Don't give them back no matter what!
Give back my pants, damn it!
Those are my best!
Scatter!
Let's go!
Fine then!
He's coming after us!
You know that even you all can't do anything against me!
Even if it's just one of you!
Deliver them to Straw Hat-san!
Get them to the scrap island!
Strong Right!
Run!
To southeast!
What's with all the ruckus?!
A pervert...!
Franky is rampaging!
Again?!
No! The town could be destroyed!
Wait, damn it!
Hey! That guy isn't wearing anything!
Ah! Look at the...!
Get the kids inside the houses!
Don't let them see the pervert!
Strong Right!
He's committing a crime, arrest him!
D-Deliver the pants!
Get on the cornetfish!
Alright! Go!
The backstreets has become a battlefield!
Damn, my leg is...!
It's no use!
Is this it?
Hey! Pass them over here!
Throw them here!
Straw Hat-san!
Straw Hat!
Definitely received them!
You...!
Straw Hat!
Did you like the ship?!
Yeah!
I've never seen such an amazing ship before!
Thanks!
Pervert! Get out of here!
Give him the death penalty!
Perverted bastard!
Of course!
It includes my super designs!
It's the answer to all of your requests!
Did you see the Soldier Dock System I invented?!
Not yet!
It'll surely be the one you'll like the most!
What about the fish pond?
I saw it!
If you put the fish you've caught in the fish pond, you can see them in the large aquarium in the room below.
It's an aquarium observation room!
Everyone should have a meal there once.
You can always eat fresh fish!
I'm looking forward to it!
That ship, for me and also for you is...
The supreme dream ship!
You bastard...!
Give back my pants!
Chopper!
Right!
H-Here he comes!
We're counting on you Roronoa-san and the other guy!
Leave it to us!
Get in there!
Target; Scrap Island!
What're you trying to do?!
The Franky Family special product!
The Shoot Anything Cannon!
Hey, hey you!
Stop joking aroun...!
Instead of his pants, he went there first!
Grab on, Chopper!
Rubber...
Rocket!
That's something accursed!
Idiot! It's just the pervert!
A cocoon! A cocoon! A cocoon!
B-Brother!
What's with this situation?!
Franky!
Thanks for the ship!
It's the best ship!
We'll treasure it!
Yeah!
I pray for you to have a safe trip.
If you want these pants back,
You'll have to become our crewmate!
Put on your pants!
Pervert!
He destroyed the city again!
Get out of here, pervert!
You idiot!
Give back my pants, Straw Hat.
Then, join our crew.
Don't be stupid!
Don't think just because you got my pants, you can make me your crewmate!
What
kind
of
man
isthat
who,
even
naked
faces straight
the countless
waves
as
it
would
bea
lion
He decided to pose with his lower half exposed!
Don't look!
It's the worst!
He's the worst!
I took him lightly!
How determinated!
He's a man inside a man!
He's just a pervert!
If I might get a little rough...
Can I give a hand?
Dos Fleur!
Two Flowers
Grab!
Eh?! Wait a sec, Robin!
They have been grabbed! Ouch!
They'll be smashed, Robin!
They'll be torn off!
They'll be taken off!
Just like an orange!
Hey, Robin!
I want him to be still a man when he becomes our crewmate!
Don't take them!
It hurts just by looking!
What's going on?
Franky is taking damage!
What? It's like a scream when a chicken's head is being tied up!
I feel bad for him.
Even though he's a pervert.
Just like when a treasure is in front of a pirate and he doesn't want to let go.
If I don't receive a good reason,
I'm not letting you go.
T-That's why...!
I told you I can't leave this island...
I'm grateful to you guys...
But that's something impossible for me to do.
I want to go with you but...
There are still things I must do here.
That's why I gave you the ship.
I quit being a shipwright to begin with.
That's why, that one is the only ship I'll ever build again.
I had only one wish...
And that is.. the dream ship over there!
Wait, Franky...
That still hasn't become the dream ship you talked about.
Dream ship?
That's right!
That ship won't be one that will be completed just with the blueprints.
It'll sail many seas!
Overcome many battles and difficulties...
And when it reaches the end of the sea...
That's when it'll be called a dream ship!
Then, someday, when I complete that awesome ship,
I'll board it and become its shipwright!
I'm looking forward to see that fateful day!
By then the ship might be all worn out but,
Surely, it'll shine much more than any other ship out there!
How is it? Amazing, isn't it, Tom-san?
Yes, it's amazing.
And if you get on it and take care of it...
You will have surpassed me!
It's that pirate blood of yours.
Dumb-Franky, do you really think you can surpass Tom-san?
What was that?!
Bastard! What're you doing?!
Damn Dumb-Franky!
What, if you're a man do it with a bang!
The things I wanted to do have changed!
The things you wanted?
You're wrong.
You now, have done everything you had to do in this island.
Atonement!
That day...
You blamed yourself and regretted the capture of Tom-san.
But Tom-san has already forgiven you.
Showing you a new path.
You collected thugs from the backstreets,
Made a name for yourselves as bounty hunters,
Protected this island from plunderers,
You protected everything Tom-san loved in this Water Metropolis,
Everything to atone for your guilt.
You might not see it from that point of view.
Of course I don't...
I didn't intend that in the least.
You stopped making those ships you liked, to keep living.
Do you plan to keep doing that from here on?
Even though Tom-san has already forgiven you,
Even though I have already forgiven you,
It won't change anything, right?
It's time...
To forgive yourself, Franky!
Live for your dream now!
What...?!
A bag?
It's the luggage for your trip, Brother!
Move it, you!
Ah! The Franky Family!
Brother!
Those guys...!
Brother, please forgive us for everything!
We're really sorry!
Really sorry!
We're prepared to take any punishment.
We're idiots, so...!
This was all we could plan!
What were you planning?!
A way to steal my pants?!
A way to turn me into a pirate?!
Don't butt in!
This is my life!
I'll decide everything!
Does the way you, my followers, are making me walk delight you?!
It's shameful!
If you thought this through,
You shouldn't have in the first place!
There's no excuse but...
Is it bad if we care for you a little?
For the one who picked us up when were just plunderers...
Is it bad if we care for your happiness?!
Who's the idiot?
You guys...
B-Brother...
Hey! Robin!
Please don't overdo it! I beg of you!
He'll turn into a woman!
He's crying!
Damn it, Nico Robin!
I won't forgive you!
It hurts so much that I can't stop crying!
Robin!
Have you stopped?
All I did, was just start this.
He sure is clever.
Blaming the pain for those tears.
Just start it?
Damn!
I can't stop crying!
Brother!
Are you okay?!
There's no way I could be okay!
It seems you haven't noticed...
What's with this speedo guy?
You shouldn't show up in these backstreets.
Zambai!
This time, the backstreets of Water Seven will be controlled by Franky!
It's a pleasure!
Y-Yes!
Brother!
Ah! This is good!
We should come again.
It's a bro who goes outside in a speedo.
Would you like to have a drink with us?
We'll show you the way to the bar.
W-What're you doing?!
Let go of us!
Little girls shouldn't drink sake during daytime!
I happen to know a nice store where we can drink some good cola.
How about it?
Would you like to?
Brother! Brother!
Food... please...
All the guys who haven't eaten, follow me!
Rampage all you want!
It's the raising of the Franky Family!
Franky! Franky! Franky!
You...
If I'm not here, how can you survive...?
Brother...
We'll test our strength with new tasks in Water Seven...!
And show we can definitely succeed!
Please be at ease!
Brother, don't cry!
Brother!
Even if Brother goes far away...
We will always be your followers!
Brother!
I can't stop crying...!
Hurry!
This is bad!
Luffy!
Zoro, Sanji.
We're in big trouble!
Your grandpa came back, Luffy!
He's at the opposite coast making arrangements to attack and is looking for us!
Huh?! Why?!
Didn't he decide not to capture us?!
How should we know?!
Hurry up and prepare to leave!
Franky! Bastard, you're not wearing your pants yet?!
Here you go!
Well then, get on, Franky.
On my ship.
Stop talking so cocky!
The only repairs you amateurs are capable of, are cheap ones.
If there isn't one shipwright in this splendid ship...
I would pity the ship.
It can't be helped.
I'll give you a hand!
Your ship's shipwright...
Will be the great Franky!
Alright! A new crewmate!
Alright!
Brother!
Don't cry...!
Don't cry!
Straw Hat-san is a man of trust!
Tom-san...
I'm... leaving this island...
I was nothing but a troublesome student, however...
Did you hear, the news from scrap island?!
Tom's Workers finished the sea train, you say?!
Thank you for looking after me!
Galley-La head shipwrights.
Iceburg, I'm counting on you!
You were also a troublesome student...
Old lady Kokoro...
Little ones...
Yokozuna...
Pervert!
Lively townspeople...
Where are you going?!
You'll come back, right?!
My little sisters...
Sodom.
Gomorrah.
And...
My beloved followers!
I'll be leaving for a while!
Put on your pants.
Translation, Cornman @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Initial timing, Hedi @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Quality checking, Sewil
Editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, MaideV and Halee
Raw providing, SOFCJ-Raws